-[Caine]: [upbeat] Welcome to the
Amazing Digital Circus Awards Show...
[flatly]
Charity Auction.
[Southern accent] We are so blessed
to have your wonderful faces here today
for this little hootenanny of ours!
The Awards Show ended up
going over budget,
would you believe,
and we need to make back
them lost trillion smackeroonies!
-[Pomni]: Wait, did money become a thing?
-[Caine]: Pomni, look at me!
Bubble!
-[Faux Bubble]: Mmyep?
-[Caine]: What do we have first
on the menu, boy?
-[Faux Bubble]: I'm Bubble.
-[Ragatha]: W-Wait, is that me?
-[Caine]: You bet
your sweet sea bisket it is!
With this one of a kind --
I say, ONE OF A KIND keychain,
you're sure to get heads spinnin'
with this dangling doofus!
Now, shall we start the biddin'
at 1,000 Loonies?
Do I hear 1,000 Loonies?
How about 1,000 Toonies?
[unintelligible rapid speech]
Sold to the ragdoll down in front!
-[Ragatha]: But I didn't --
-[Faux Bubble]: No refunds, [BOINK!]
-[Caine]: Bubble, why you sound
like a complete fool?
[teeth chattering]
Holy hotdog, Bubble,
I'm seein' four!
-[Bubble]: That's my cousin --
La Buble.
-[Faux Bubble]: The "L" is silent.
-[Caine]: Whaddya mean there are two --
Am I hearing two
Bubbles to Bubbles?
Hmm...
[whispering unintelligibly]
-The Amazing Digital Circus.
-[Bubble]: I don't give a [HONK!]
-[Caine]: [clears throat]
The Bubble plush!
-[Faux Bubble]: Wait, wha--
-[Caine]: Why not spice up your life
with this little fella!
He's squishy, soft, and with a tongue
that's full of diseases!
How could anyone resist that?
I say, how could anyone resist that?
I got nothin'.
Nothin' over here,
nothin' over there.
[rapid unintelligible speech]
[tragic music plays]
-[Evil Pomni]:
Ugh, [HONK!], man.
This is so lame.
Hey, dental plan.
I'd like to buy this bad [BOINK!]-boy
if you're selling him.
-[Jax]: [laughs] Oh, you.
-[Evil Jax]: I-I'd buy Pomni over here...
To protect me from him.
-[Evil Pomni]: Why do you have to be
so [SWOOSH!] stupid?
-[Evil Jax]: Please stop yelling at me...
-[Kinger]: [backwards speech]
-[Caine]: The Machine...
-[The Machine]: I'm the MaMa!
-[Jax-Pomni]:
[chuckles] Hey.
'Sup, losers?
-[Caine]: A creation gone wrong,
or horribly right!
The rare combination
of stoner and fool,
an absolute complete menace
to themselves.
-[Jax-Pomni]:
Who the [BOINK] is this guy?
-[Evil Jax]: Oh, God!
[shrieks]
-[Jax-Pomni]: Come on.
I just wanna, like,
not hurt you, or anything.
I don't see a name on it,
so it's mine now.
-[Caine]: Oh,
this isn't working, Bubble.
We need... the MODEL...
[thudding footsteps approaching]
[sinister music plays]
♪♪
-[deep voice] Hey, guys.
-[Faux Bubble]: Now you and your --
-[Caine]: Away with you, imposter!
[pop!]
Show your dominance
by wearing these "I can fix him"
or "I can make her worse" shirts!
Featuring everyone's favorite
mentally ill duo!
-[Faux Bubble]:
Or, if you're a Canadian freak...
-[Caine]: Wait --
-[Faux Bubble]: Why not this comfy sweater
with all your favorite [BLEEP!]
on the back!
-[Caine]: And why stop there?
Wear in mourning
your abstracted friends
on the worst body part
God ever made -- the ear.
Kinger, you're a fascist!
Would you like
a new set of glamorous --
-[Kinger]: Well, I --
-[Caine]: [rapid unintelligible speech]
-[Kinger]: Oh,
this is exciting, isn't it?
-[Disappearing Guy]:
I'll buy your --
-[Caine]: Do you like to work hard,
or do you like to hardly work it?
This one of a kind,
one-size-fits-all gamin' mat
is sure to spice up
your hardly workin'.
Do I --
[chaos]
[slowed speech]
Hootenanny --
Sold to the man without a shirt!
Wait, where da mat go?
-[Jax-Pomni]: No!
You [BOING!] suck, man.
Yeah, I'm pulling your IP address
as we speak -- dick.
-[Caine]: [huffs] I'm on the verge
of losing my mind, Bubble.
How are we doing so far?
How much did we make back?
-[Bubble]: Doing basic math,
judging by all the items sold,
I'd say we made
a grand total of zero.
-[Faux Bubble]: The circus is saved!
[off-key music plays]
-[Kinger]:
Oh, are we at an auction?
-[Evil Jax]: [weakly]
Stop, this is embarrassing...
-[Jax-Pomni]: Laugh out loud.
-[Caine]: Oh, boy,
here come the demons!
-[Gangle]: What's that?
-[Zooble]: I don't know.
But I love how it shakes.
-[Kinger]: Yeah --
and it looks like Caine, too.
I want one.
-[Manager Gangle]: Yeah -- me, too!
I can put that on my pencil case,
or my pantzzzzzzz...
-[Jax-Pomni]:
Go on and keep shaking!
-[all]: Shake, shake, shake!
-[Caine]: Go on and shake me!
Go on and shake me!!
GO ON AND SHAKE MEEEEEEE--
[babbling]
[brief backwards speech]
-Um, is this guy gonna be okay?
Should we --
We should call an ambulance.
This is bad.
-[Caine]: [babbling continues throughout]
[cheerful western music plays]
♪♪